伙计们  你们一定不会相信
Guys, you won't believe this!
-我刚刚跟我的经纪人谈过  -我的天啊
- I just talked to my agent... - Oh, my God!
对不起  反应太快了  你说吧
I'm sorry. Too soon. You go.
我因为《我们的日子》被提名了
I got nominated for my part on Days of our Lives!
-这真的是太好了  -恭喜你
- Good for you! - Congratulations!
我不敢相信你竟然获得艾美奖提名了
I can't believe you're nominated for an Emmy!
-不是  -肥皂剧文摘奖
- No, no. - Soap Opera Digest Award?
不  我被"肥皂奖"提名了
Nope. I'm up for a "Soapie."
那是你乱编的名字吗
Honey, is that something you're making up?
不  真有这个奖
No, no, no, it's real!
从1998年开始颁发
And it has been, since 1998.
瑞秋  我被提名肥皂奖了
Hey, Rach! I'm up for a Soapie!
我的天啊   天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
那可是排名第三的肥皂剧大奖
That's the third most prestigious soap opera award there is!
谢谢  我知道该带谁参加颁奖典礼了
Thank you! I guess we know who I'll take to the awards!
别跟我开这种玩笑  各路明星都会去吗
Stop that! Don't kid about that! Will all the stars be there?
很多明星都说他们会去
Many are scheduled to appear.
天啊  我不能去  我一定会太过紧张
Oh, my god. I can't go. I'll be too nervous!
-那就换我去吧  -不行
- I'll go. - No.
你都要结婚了  我就只能靠颁奖礼乐呵乐呵了
You're getting married. This is all I have.
恩斯特·穆伯拉特首先猜测
And it was Ernst Muhlbrat who first hypothesized
迅猛龙受到威胁时  会把颈部肌肉张开
that the Velociraptor, when threatened, would expand it's collar
发出尖锐的叫声...
and emit a high-pitched noise...
将敌人吓跑
...to frighten off predators.
路易斯  什么事
Yes, Mr. Lewis?
什么样的叫声
What kind of noise?
就是一种尖锐  骇人的声音
Just a high-pitched, intimidating noise.
那到底是什么样子
But like how?
我们并不确定
Well, we don't know for sure.
但我想  应该是这样的
But in my head, it sounded something like this:
当然  这只是种猜侧
Of course, this is just conjecture.
好了  今天的课上到这里
Okay. That's all for today.
摩斯  我能跟你谈谈吗
Mr. Morse, can I see you for a moment?
什么事  教授
Yes, sir?
我得跟你谈谈你的期中考成绩
Mr. Morse, I need to talk to you about your midterm exam.
-恐怕我得把你当掉  -为什么
- I'm afraid I had to fail you. - Why?
你得答对69%才能及格
Well, you need 60% to pass.
-我的分数是多少  -七分
- What did I get? - Seven.
那可不太理想
That's not so good.
对  很不理想
No, no, it's not.
奈德  到底发生了什么事
What happened, Ned?
希望你可以饶我一次
Maybe you can cut me some slack.
我恋爱了
I'm sort of in love.
抱歉  但那不是我的问题
I'm sorry, but that's really not my problem.
我爱上了你
I'm in love with you.
那好像跟我有一点关系
That brings me in the loop a little.
所以我才会考那么烂
That's why I did so bad on this test.
我没办法专心上课
I'm having a hard time concentrating.
你站在讲台上讲课的时候...
When you're up there and you're teaching...
表情是那么地严肃...
...and your face gets all serious...
你看起来好帅
You look so good.
当你穿着紧身高领毛衣的时候
When you wear that tight little turtleneck sweater...
好了
Okay.
我是你的老师  对不起
I'm your teacher. I'm sorry.
你是学生
You're a student.
而且我喜欢女人
And I like women.
虽然有人在椅背上不是这么写的
In spite of what may be written on the backs of these chairs.
天啊
Oh, my god.
吧台那个男人在看你
That guy at the counter's totally checking you out.
真的吗
Really?
-天啊  他真的好帅  -上吧
- Oh, my God, he's really cute! - Go for it.
菲比  我订婚了
Phoebe, I'm engaged.
我建议你去问他要电话号码  以防万一
I'm just saying, get his number, just in case.
说不定钱德勒发生意外  丧失了性能力
But if Chandler's in an accident and can't perform sexually...
他想让你找个情人
...he'd want you to take a lover
帮他满足你的生理需求
to satisfy needs he'd no longer fulfill.
我能跟你说句话吗
Can I just tell you something?
我真的受宠若惊  但我订婚了
I'm very flattered, but I'm engaged.
这话说来有点难为情
This is kind of embarrassing.
事实上  我是想跟你朋友说话
I actually came over to talk to your friend.
你确实应该觉得难为情
You should be embarrassed.
我还以为你知道我是在看你
I thought you knew I was looking at you.
我知道  不过耍她真的很好玩
I did, but that was really fun.
"得奖的是...乔伊·崔比安尼"
"The winner is... Joey Tribbiani!"
我真的没想到我会得奖...
"I honestly never expected this.
我没有准备演讲稿...
I didn't prepare a speech.
我要谢谢我的父母  他们一直支持我...
I'd like to thank my parents, who've always been there for me.
我还要谢谢我的朋友
Also like to thank my friends,
钱德勒  莫妮卡  菲比  瑞秋
Chandler, Monica, Phoebe, Rachel..."
-我才排第四  -天啊
- I'm fourth? - Jeez!
瞧你啊  拿着枫糖瓶当奖杯
Look at you with your maple syrup award!
拜托你别把这事告诉别人
Maybe you don't tell anyone about this?
那没什么大不了  我也会拿洗发水瓶当奖杯
It's not a big deal. I do that too, with my shampoo bottle.
-真的吗  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
-你假装自己得了什么奖  -葛莱美奖
- What award are you practicing for? - Grammy.
我是最佳新进艺人
For Best New Artist.
肥皂奖的人今天打电话给我
Listen. The Soapies people called today.
我还得上台颁奖
I also get to present an award.
所以就算你没得奖  你也有机会上台
That's great. So you'll get on stage even if you don't win.
-你觉得我不会得奖  -你当然会得奖
- You don't think I'll win? - Of course I do.
但最受欢迎死而复生奖
But Favorite Returning Character?
那个奖项竞争很激烈
That's a tough category, Joey.
你要跟一个火葬了之后还能活过来的人竞争
You're up against the guy who survived his own cremation.
不  我知道自己或许不会得奖  只是...
No, I know I might not win. But it's just...
我从来没有被提过名  我真的很想得奖
I've never been nominated before. I want it so much.
或许你会得奖
You'll probably get it.
但你应该开始练习"输得起"的表情了
But you should start practicing your "gracious-loser" face.
当摄影机拍到你时  你得表现出失望的样子
When the cameras are on you, you want to look disappointed.
但也要摆出对方是实至名归的表情
But also that your colleague deserved to win.
就像这样
It's sort of like:
你知道吗
You know?
你也练习过自己没得到葛莱美奖的情况
You practice losing the Grammys too?
不  我是葛莱美奖的常胜军
No, at the Grammys, I always win.
你跟杰克约会还顺利吗
How'd your date go with Jake?
很不错  我们整晚一直注视着彼此
Great. We couldn't keep our eyes off each other all night.
每隔一阵子
Every once in a while,
他就会靠过来轻抚我的头发跟脖子
he'd lean over, stroke my hair, then touch my neck.
住手  菲比  你害得我好痒
Stop it, Phoebe. You're getting me all tingly.
我心里一直在想  他要吻我了吗
All I could think of was, is he gonna kiss me? Is he gonna kiss me?
他吻了你吗
Did he?
我是个淑女  绝不会泄露这种私事
I'm a lady, Monica. I don't kiss and tell.
但这个吻痕说明了一切
But this hickey speaks for itself.
好了  我知道了
Okay, I got it. I got it.
我真的好喜欢他
I like him so much,
我今天像是喝了十杯酒那么飘飘欲仙
I feel like I've had 10 drinks today.
其实我只喝了六杯
I've only had six.
我开始跟钱德勒约会后再也没有那样的感觉了
I haven't had that feeling since I first went out with Chandler.
我永远都不会再有那样的感觉了
I'll never have that feeling again.
你的口气跟男人一模一样
You sound like a guy.
不  男人会说"我永远都不能再跟别人上床"
No, a guy would say, "I'll never get to sleep with anyone else."
我永远都不能再跟别人上床
I'll never sleep with anyone else!
我一直忙着筹备婚礼
I'm so busy planning the wedding,
完全忘了自己要舍弃什么
I forgot about what I'll give up.
我再也不会有初吻了
I'll never have a first kiss again.
你会有最后的吻别
You'll have a last kiss.
我能问你一件事吗  有男人喜欢过你吗
Can I ask you something? Has a guy ever had a crush on you?
所以你才要帮我打领带吗
Is that why you wanted to tie my tie?
我班上的学生说他爱上我了
There's a kid in my class who said he's in love with me.
-什么事这么惊讶  -罗斯有男朋友了
- Whoa, what? - Ross has a boyfriend!
我没有男朋友
I do not have a boyfriend.
我班上有个男学生暗恋我
There's a guy in one of my classes who has a crush on me.
-真的吗  -对
- Really? - Yeah, I don't know.
去年是伊莉莎白  现在又是这个孩子...
Last year, Elizabeth, now this kid...
这是怎么回事  难道我散发出...
What is it? Am I giving out some kind of...
性感教授的气质吗
...sexy-professor vibe?
现在没看出来
Not right now.
重点是我的天生丽质害他挂了期中考试
The point is, my natural charisma has made him fail his midterm.
我为那孩子感到可惜
Now I feel bad for the kid.
我也曾经暗恋过老师  真的很难受
I had a crush on a teacher once, and it was so hard.
我没办法专心上课
I couldn't concentrate.
每次他看着我  我都会脸红
I blushed every time he looked at me.
你还记得十九岁时恋爱的滋味吧
You remember what it's like to be 19 and in love.
-我可以放他一马  -太棒了
- I can cut him some slack. - Yeah.
你怎么忘记那个老师的
How'd you get over that teacher?
我没忘  我跟他上床了
I didn't. I got under him.
问题解决了
Problem solved.
-再见  菲比  -好  再见
- Bye, Phoebe. - Okay, bye.
-好  再见  -再见
- All right. Bye. - Bye.
我们在门口说再见  不想炫耀我们的新恋情
We said goodbye at the door so as not to flaunt our new love.
没关系  你不必顾忌我
It's okay. You don't have to tiptoe around me.
我已经想过了  你知道吗
I've thought about it. You know what?
我可以接受没有再次心动感觉的生活
I'm okay about not having that new-relationship feeling.
-我已经开始想你了  -我也想你
- I miss you already! - I miss you too!
这就是我所说的  你们很甜蜜
See? That's what I mean. I mean that, that's great,
但我不会拿自己的幸福跟你交换
but I wouldn't trade what I have for that.
我会一辈子跟钱德勒相守
I'll be with Chandler the rest of my life.
这让我觉得很幸福
That makes me happy.
亲爱的  快坐下
Sweetie, come here. Come sit down.
我们正在谈我们的关系
Phoebe and I were just talking about
有多深厚  多么意义重大
how our relationship's deep and meaningful.
-确实是那样  你觉得呢  -一点都没错
- It really is, don't you think? - Oh, totally.
拉一下我的手指
Pull my finger.
最受欢迎死而复生的男演员...
Favorite Returning Male...
轮到我了
This is my category!
-你的演讲稿带了吗  -带了
- Got your speech? - Got my speech.
"输得起"的表情练习好了吗
Got your gracious-loser face?
记住  如果你得奖了  你得抱我
Try to remember, if you win, you have to hug me.
-抱我  -好
- Hug me. - Okay.
我能捏你屁股吗
Can I squeeze your ass?
在电视上吗
On TV?
可以
Yeah!
最受欢迎死而复生男演员奖被提名的有
In the Favorite Returning Male character category, the nominees are:
约翰·惠勒  《综合医院》
John Wheeler from General Hospital.
盖文·格雷厄姆  《年少轻狂》
Gavin Graham from The Young and the Restless.
邓肯·哈灵顿  《热情》
Duncan Harrington from Passions.
乔伊·崔比安尼  《我们的日子》
And Joey Tribbiani from Days of our Lives.
得奖的是
And the Soapie goes to:
盖文·格雷厄姆  《年少轻狂》
Gavin Graham from The Young and the Restless.
搞什么...
What the...?!
颁发最受欢迎女配角奖的是
Presenting the award for Favorite Supporting Actress
《我们的日子》中的乔伊·崔比安尼
is Joey Tribbiani from Days of our Lives.
所有被这个奖项提名的优秀女演员...
Any one of the brilliant actresses nominated for this award...
得奖都是实至名归  可惜只有一个人能得奖
...deserves to take it home. Unfortunately, only one can.
最受欢迎女配角奖被提名的有
The nominees for Favorite Supporting Actress are:
《热情》  艾玲·高菲
From Passions, Erin Goff.
《一生一次》  玛丽·劳伦·比索普
From One Life to Live, Mary Lauren Bishop.
《我的孩子们》  莎拉·蕾妮
From All My Children, Sarah Renee.
《我们的日子》  杰西卡·艾什莉
And from Days of our Lives, Jessica Ashley.
得奖的是
And the winner is:
杰西卡·艾什莉  《我们的日子》
Jessica Ashley from Days of our Lives.
可惜的是  杰西卡今晚因故无法出席...
Unfortunately, Jessica couldn't be with us tonight...
我将代表她接受这个奖项
...so I'll accept this award on her behalf.
我相信杰西卡...
And I'm sure that Jessica...
会想感谢我的父母...
...wants to thank my parents...
他们一直都很支持我
...who always believed in me.
她也想感谢我的朋友
She'd also like to thank my friends:
钱德勒  莫妮卡  罗斯
Chandler, Monica, Ross,
菲比  跟瑞秋...
Phoebe and Rachel...
她就坐在那边
...who's sitting right there.
我们为什么要急匆匆离开
Joey, why'd we have to rush out of there so fast?
我们得赶快离开  因为...
We had to get out of there because...
你看我拿了什么回家
Look what I won!
我的天啊  你偷走了她的奖杯
Oh, my God. You stole her award!
不  是我代表她收下了
No, no, no. I'm accepting it on her behalf.
你大概不知道"代表"是什么意思
I don't think you know what "behalf" means.
我当然知道
Sure I do.
这是个动词  意思是"我能分一半"
It's a verb. As in "I be half-in' it"!
乔伊
Joey.
你得还回去
You've got to take this back.
为什么  我应该得奖的  我真的好想得奖
Why? I should've won. I really wanted it.
她根本不在乎  都没有出席
She didn't care enough to come to the thing.
它也可以拿来当葛莱美
It could also be a Grammy.
-不行  乔伊  -别这样  瑞秋
- No, Joey. - Come on, Rach.
没人看到我把它拿走  整个桌子上都是奖杯
No one saw me take it. There's a whole table of them.
你真的想要一个不属于自己的奖杯吗
Do you want an award you didn't win?
不  我想要属于自己的奖杯
No, I want an award I did win.
但没有人愿意让我得奖
But nobody's given me any of those!
如果我把它摆在那里
Plus, if I put it up there, when people come over,
大家就会看到  以为我真的得奖了
they'll see it and think I won it.
乔伊  上面写着"最佳女配角奖"
Joey, it says "Best Supporting Actress."
我可以把那个刮掉
I can scratch that right off.
乔伊  这么做不对  你得还回去
Joey, no, this is wrong. You have to take it back.
这样把奖杯拿回家没有意义
You don't want to win an award this way.
你真的有演戏天份
You're very talented.
总有一天你会得奖
Someday you'll win one of these for real
那对你来说才有意义
and that one will mean something.
-好吧  -好吗  谢谢
- Oh, all right. - All right? Thank you.
-我明天就还回去  -谢谢
- I'll take it back tomorrow. - Thank you.
如果我不能拥有  那你也别想拥有
If I can't have it, you can't have it!
盖勒教授
Professor Geller?
路易斯  有什么事吗
Yes, Mr. Lewis? How can I help you?
我知道我的期中考试没有考好
I know I didn't do well on my midterms and stuff.
但我希望你能帮我改成绩
But I was hoping you could change my grade.
我为什么要帮你改
And why, exactly, would I do that?
因为我爱上你了
Because I'm in love with you.
什么
What?
对  我爱上你了
Yeah. I'm all in love with you and stuff.
-你可以帮我改成绩吗  -不行
- So could you change my grade? - No!
为什么  你都帮奈德改了
Why not? You changed Ned's grade.
那不一样  因为他真的爱上我了
That's different. Because he was actually in love with me.
不  他才没有  他只是在耍你
No, he's not! He's totally yanking your chain.
他已经用这一招对付过其他三个教授了
He's done this with three other teachers.
-什么  -他有女朋友
- What? - He's got a girlfriend.
我不敢相信有人会为了成绩出此下策
I can't believe someone would do that for a grade.
就是嘛
I know.
太不厚道了
It's awful.
我爱你
I love you.
你看到钱德勒了吗
- Have you seen Chandler? - No, why?
我一直在想我将要失去的一切
I keep thinking about all the things I won't have.
我很惶恐  我不知道该怎么办
It's freaking me out. I don't know what to do about it.
别担心
Don't sweat it.
钱德勒不在
Chandler's not around,
别管那么多规矩
so go ahead and get it out of your system.
那个男的很帅
That guy's cute.
别这样  我是认真的
Phoebe, come on, I'm serious.
我得跟他谈谈这件事
I've got to talk to him about this.
这种事怎么能跟他谈呢
That's the last thing you want to do.
-为什么  -因为你要嫁给他了
- Why? - Because you're marrying him!
你得帮帮我
You gotta help me out here.
我从来没有订过婚  也没有结过婚
I've never been engaged. I've never really been married.
我只能告诉你我妈告诫我的话
I can only tell you what my mother told me.
当你对一段关系有疑惑  害怕或焦虑时
When you have doubts or fears or anxieties about a relationship...
别跟你的丈夫沟通这些问题
...don't communicate them to your husband.
我不能跟我要共度一生的男人...
I'm not supposed to share my doubts and fears...
分享我的疑惑跟恐惧
...with the guy I'm spending the rest of my life with?
没错  就是那样
That is correct. Yes.
你应该把那件事放在心里...
You're supposed to put all that stuff in a little box in your mind...
永不再提
...and lock it up tight.
-那是你妈告诫你的  -对
- Your mother told you this? - Yes.
那个结过很多次婚
The woman who married a bunch of times
在你十三岁时就自杀的女人
and killed herself when you were 13?
我的天啊  你说得对
Oh, my God, you're right.
快去告诉钱德勒  快点  免得太迟了
Go! Go tell Chandler. Hurry, before it's too late!
等一下  这表示放荡是得不到真爱的吗
Wait! Does this also mean that putting out doesn't get you love?
-我就要见到杰西卡·艾什莉了  -等一下
- I cannot believe I'm gonna meet Jessica Ashley! - Wait, wait.
瑞秋  拜托你矜持一点  好吗
Rach, please be cool, okay?
我跟这个女人一起工作
I work with this woman.
好吧  我会很矜持的
Okay, I'm totally cool.
请进
Come in.
-杰西卡  -杰西
- Hey, Jessica. - Hey, Jess.
她是我朋友瑞秋
This is my friend Rachel.
你好吗
What's up?
这是你的肥皂奖  我代表你领了奖
Here's your Soapie. I accepted it for you.
天啊  我得奖了
Oh, my God. I won?
你知道这意味着吗
Do you have any idea what this means?
你不把奖杯摆在柜子里吗
That's it? You're not gonna put it on your shelf or anything?
不  只有真正的奖杯才配摆在柜子里
No, I try to save that for real awards.
失陪
Now if you'll excuse me?
-要拿回去吗  -那当然
- Take it back? - Absolutely.
对  干得漂亮
Yeah, you do!
亲爱的  我们快结婚了...
Honey? As we get closer to the wedding...
你有什么事想跟我分享吗
...is there anything you'd like to talk about and share?
好吧  我觉得桌上的装饰物太大了
Okay. I think the centerpieces are too big.
才没有  装饰物尺寸刚刚好
You're wrong. The centerpieces are fine.
你曾经害怕过吗
Do you ever get scared at all?
有一点  那玩意真的很大
Kind of. They're really big.
你不害怕自己
Doesn't it ever freak you out
没办法再结识新的伴侣吗
that you'll never be with anybody new again?
什么
What?
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
我一想到不会再有心动的感觉就觉得难过
Sometimes it bothers me that I'll never have that feeling.
当你刚刚认识一个人
When you meet someone for the first time
会觉得新鲜刺激  你知道那种心动的感觉吗
...and it's new and exciting. You know that rush?
不
No.
不  当我刚刚认识一个人...
No, when I first meet somebody...
我会觉得慌张  焦虑  满头大汗
...it's mostly panic, anxiety and a great deal of sweating.
好吧  但你是男人
Okay. But you're a guy.
你不害怕你永远不能再跟别人上床吗
Does it not freak out that you'll never sleep with anybody else?
不能跟别人上床  不
Sleeping with somebody, no.
我害怕的是焦虑  慌张  满头大汗
Anxiety, panic and, I'm afraid, even more sweating.
即使是我跟在一起
Even with me?
我们刚开始交往的六个月
I was dangerously dehydrated
我严重脱水
the first six months of our relationship.
对我来说
For me, the rush is knowing
一想到我们会共度余生就觉得心动
that we'll be together the rest of our lives.
-真的吗  -对
- Really? - Well, yeah.
但知道你有这些想法
But now that I know that you're having these thoughts,
我又找回了慌张  焦虑跟...
we're back to panic, anxiety and...
我真的需要喝点运动饮料
...I'll definitely need some kind of sports drink.
过来  你不必担心
Come here. Oh, you don't have to worry.
而且你知道吗
Besides, you know what?
跟你在一起  我一定会惊喜不断
I'll have a lot of new things with you.
我们第一次买房子
The first time we buy a house.
第一个孩子  第一个孙子
Our first kid. Our first grandkid.
给我水  快点
Water. Water. Water.
摩斯  我能跟你谈谈吗
Mr. Morse? Can I speak to you for a moment?
你今天的课上得很精彩  你剪了头发吗
That was a great lecture today. Did you get a little haircut?
对  你喜欢吗  你爱我的发型吗
Yeah, yeah. Do you like it? Do you love it?
我要告诉你  我会把你的成绩改回来
I want you to know I'm changing your grade back.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
我知道你在搞什么鬼  那样是行不通的
I know what you're trying to pull here. It won't work.
我没有搞鬼  听着  我爱你
I'm not trying to pull anything. Look, I love you, dude.
我根本不想谈这件事
I'm not even gonna talk about this.
这件"风流韵事"结束了
This little "thing" is over.
我知道你有女朋友
I know you have a girlfriend.
也知道其他教授的事了
And I know about the other professors.
知道这些我会有什么感觉  你利用了我
How do you think that makes me feel, Ned? You used me!
你不爱我  你从来都没爱过我
You don't love me and you never did!
温斯顿教授  佛迪瑞克森教授
Professor Winston. Professor Frederickson.
我马上来
I'll be right with you.
别把这件事搞大  我会给你"丙"
Don't make this worse and I'll give you a "C."
我们可以走了吗
Shall we?
-瑞秋  -我马上来
- Rach. - I'll be out in a second.
这简直太意外了
"It's just so unexpected!
我得告诉大家  被提名诺贝尔奖...
I'll tell you, it's such an honor to just be nominated...
已经是莫大的光荣
...for a Nobel Prize.
而我竟然因为按摩得了诺贝尔奖
And, you know, to win one for a massage!
特别是我刚拿下东尼奖的最佳女演员奖...
Especially just after winning a Tony Award for Best Actress..."
我们订了八点的位置
Honey, we have to go. Our reservations are at 8.
以《我们订了八点的位置》一剧
"...in Reservations at Eight.
得奖编剧是尼尔·西蒙
by Neil Simon.
谢谢你  尼尔  谢谢你写的台词
Thank you, Neil. Thank you for the words."
待会再玩  我们要迟到了  赶紧走
Okay honey, you can finish this later we're gonna be late. We gotta go.
请先不要奏乐  我就说最后一句
Please don't play the music. Just one more thing.
"纽约现场直播欢迎收看《周末夜现场》"
"Live from New York, it's Saturday Night!"